very good sweetheart this is bringing
muy buena corazón es que está le trae
attention to this bombshell okay we're shocked we have to
atención a este bombazo vale nos hemos
talk about things okay and
tenemos que hablar cositas vale y quiero
right now I
que ahora mismo todo el mundo que esté
want everyone who's watching this video to sign up for the next hour 8:30 in the evening here it's interesting to the CEO with Enrique Garcia and Francisco Rodriguez tonight we'll talk we'll give a lot of exclusives okay we'll tell you a lot of things that they don't tell you anywhere
muchas cositas que no cuentan en ninguna
else
otra parte
bombshell that Rocío Flores just dropped
bombazo que acaba de soltar rocío flores
at the end of Ana Rosa's program and it is
al cierre del programa de ana rosa' y es
that she gave an exclusive in
que ha dado una exclusiva en la revista
Semana magazine the Semanas magazine has already
semana la revista semanas ya se ha
become I
convertido
think officially the
creo que oficialmente en la revista de
flagship magazine of the Flores family no Antonio
cabecera de la familia flores no antonio
Ave Olga and now Rocío Flores not
ave olga y ahora rocío flores no
exclusive she shows off her spectacular figure for the first time it's
exclusiva luce por primera vez su
been a bad time
espectacular figura lo he pasado mal
but now I'm a new woman let's see she comes
pero ahora soy una mujer nueva a ver
out spectacular she comes out gorgeous
sale espectacular sale guapísima
gorgeous Rocío Flores I'm glad she
guapísima rocío flores me alegro que
did this photo shoot tomorrow
haya hecho esta sesión de fotos mañana
we'll enjoy it okay first thing in the morning I
la disfrutaremos vale a primera hora me
'll be informed of what she says in the
estaré informando de lo que cuente en la
magazine I don't know if she'll get very wet on the
revista no sé si se mojara mucho sobre
topics what are you waiting for okay
los temas que estáis esperando vale
obviously about the second  season
evidentemente sobre la segunda temporada
of the series about her mother I don't think she'll
de la serie de su madre no creo que se
really say anything if she says anything it's going to
pronuncie realmente si dice algo va a
be something very brief you know in her
ser algo muy escueto ya sabéis en su
line of the stick well nothing once again I don't
línea del palo pues nada una vez más no
know what I don't think she'll say many things
sé qué no creo que diga muchas cosas
about the subject of Marta's relationship
sobre el tema de la relación de marta
with her father either she doesn't have anything to
con su padre tampoco tiene ya nada que
add it's already been made clear that the relationship is going
añadir ya quedó claro que la relación va
better that she wants her
mejor que ella quiere la felicidad de su
father's happiness she is passionate about her father and you
padre ella tiene pasión por su padre y
know it right and evidently she wishes him to
lo sabéis no y evidentemente le desea
be happy and she also wishes
que sea feliz y también le desea que sea
Olga to be happy with whom she also has
feliz a olga con la que también mantiene
a great relationship and they have already been
una relación estupenda y ya se les ha
seen together having coffee having breakfast
visto juntos tomando café desayunando
coming out or going in I mean regarding that
saliendo entrando o sea respecto a ese
subject that at this moment I'm spraying flowers
tema que en este momento rocío flores
also don't have anything to say
tampoco que tengan nada que decir de
gossip okay I think that evidently
cotilleo vale yo creo que evidentemente
here what she's going to talk about is the
aquí de lo que va a hablar es de la
operation the retouching that she's having
operación de los retoques que se está
done and how her life is going maybe
haciendo y de cómo va su vida a lo mejor
something about how her relationship with
algo sobre cómo está su relación con
Manuel is okay you know that he also
manuel vale que ya sabéis que también
went through a rough patch yes I at least that was what
pasó un bache si yo por lo menos eso fue
was said but she looks spectacular I mean she looks
lo que se dijo pero está espectacular o
beautiful spectacular on this
sea está guapísima espectacular en esta
cover we'll see the photograph tomorrow
portada ya veremos mañana la fotografía
Obviously we won't be able to publish them here,
evidentemente no podremos sacarlas aquí
but I'm sure some will leak on social
pero seguro que algunas se filtra en
media. Unfamiliar, what do you think about all
redes no familiar qué pensáis de todo
that? What do you think about Rocío making the
eso qué pensáis de que rocío haga una
cover? And don't forget the date we
portada y no olvidéis la cita que
have tonight at eight-thirty
tenemos esta noche a las ocho y media
here at Teles al Ceo. A hug.
aquí en teles al ceo un abrazo